songsfever.com 2011-12-25

# Our privacy policy

** We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit this site, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

**Log Files** **

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.   The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**

**DoubleClick DART Cookie** **  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.songsfever.net.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.songsfever.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html**

**Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense**

**These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.songsfever.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.**

**www.songsfever.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.**

**You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.songsfever.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.**

**If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.**

 **Last Updated: _06 April 20_** _ **11**_
